Now earlier we talked about what is in Hookah tobacco especially comparatively to cigarettes.
Hookah tobacco has got four main ingredients in it that are found in every kind of shisha you can think of.
The number one thing of course is the natural tobacco leaf.
If you are going to make your own tobacco you need to get some good quality natural tobacco leaf, dry it out, get it cut up and kind of grind that stuff up and then you want to blend that with whatever flavor you are going to be doing.
So let's say you are doing mango, you would actually blend it with the fruit, the mango flavoring and then you could mix in honey and molasses and it makes kind of syrupy thing there and then you just add more tobacco to make the right consistency that you want.
So those are the things that are in the Hookah compared to the cigarettes as you can see, four ingredients compared to 425 ingredients.
So very minimal as far as what you are intaking in your body.
There are no surprises here, you know what you are smoking.
There is nothing that you can't pronounce in Hookah tobacco.
So here is Ashli smoking some more Hookah.